<sdsapp>
	<categories last_id="12">
		<category ctime="12.12.2017 13:32:01" id="1" mtime="12.12.2017 13:32:01" ownerId="candle" slug="samplecategory1"><title>Sample category 1</title></category><category ctime="12.12.2017 14:32:01" id="2" mtime="12.12.2017 14:32:01" ownerId="candle" slug="samplecategory2"><title>Sample category 2</title></category><category ctime="12.12.2017 14:32:01" id="5" mtime="12.12.2017 14:52:01" ownerId="candle" slug="snowboarding"><title>Snowboarding</title></category><category id="6" ctime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" mtime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" ownerId="candle" slug="soccer"><title>Soccer</title></category><category id="7" ctime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" mtime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" ownerId="candle" slug="baseball"><title>Baseball</title></category><category id="8" ctime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" mtime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" ownerId="candle" slug="skiing"><title>Skiing</title></category><category id="9" ctime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" mtime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" ownerId="candle" slug="skating"><title>Skating</title></category><category id="10" ctime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" mtime="14.12.2017 13:02:13" ownerId="candle" slug="hockey"><title>Hockey</title></category><category id="11" ctime="14.12.2017 13:08:54" mtime="14.12.2017 13:08:54" ownerId="candle" slug="rockclimbing"><title>Rock Climbing</title></category><category id="12" ctime="14.12.2017 13:08:54" mtime="14.12.2017 13:08:54" ownerId="candle" slug="preferans"><title>Preferans</title></category></categories>
	<articles last_id="19">
		<article ctime="12.12.2017 15:35:01" id="3" mtime="13.12.2017 14:35:01" ownerId="candle" slug="samplearticle2" categoryId="1"><description>Sample article 2222222222 description</description><title>Sample article 2</title></article><article id="4" ownerId="candle" ctime="12.12.2017 15:32:01" mtime="14.12.2017 11:33:51" slug="snowboarding" categoryId="5"><description>Modern snowboarding began in 1965 when Sherman Poppen, an engineer in Muskegon, Michigan, invented a toy for his daughters by fastening two skis together and attaching a rope to one end so he would have some control as they stood on the board and glided downhill. Dubbed the "snurfer" (combining snow and surfer) by his wife Nancy, the toy proved so popular among his daughters' friends that Poppen licensed the idea to a manufacturer, Brunswick Corporation, that sold about a million snurfers over the next decade. And, in 1966 alone over half a million snurfers were sold.[4]</description><title>Snowboarding</title></article><article id="9" ownerId="candle" ctime="14.12.2017 12:12:16" mtime="14.12.2017 12:12:16" categoryId="5" slug="boardercross"><description>Boardercross, also known as "Boarder X" and "Snowboard X", is a very popular but relatively recent winter sport, starting in the 1980s and earning its place as an official Winter Olympic sport in the 2006 Turin games. In Boardercross, several riders (usually 4 to 6) race down a course similar to a motorcycle motocross track (with jumps, berms and other obstacles constructed out of snow on a downhill course). Unlike traditional head-to-head races, competitors use the same terrain, sometimes resulting in accidental collisions.&#13;
</description><title>Boardercross</title></article><article id="10" ownerId="candle" ctime="14.12.2017 12:15:43" mtime="14.12.2017 12:15:43" categoryId="5" slug="subculture"><title>Subculture</title><description>The snowboarding way of life came about as a natural response to the culture from which it emerged. Early on, there was a rebellion against skiing culture and the view that snowboarders were inferior. Skiers did not easily accept this new culture on their slopes. The two cultures contrasted each other in several ways including how they spoke, acted, and their entire style of clothing. Snowboarders first embraced the punk and later the hip-hop look into their style. Words such as "dude", "gnarly", and "Shred the Gnar" are some examples of words used in the snowboarding culture. Snowboarding subculture became a crossover between the urban and suburban styles on snow, which made an easy transition from surfing and skateboarding culture over to snowboarding culture.[36]&#13;
&#13;
The early stereotypes of snowboarding included "lazy", "grungy", "punk", "stoners", "troublemakers", and numerous others, many of which are associated with skateboarding and surfing as well. However, these stereotypes may be considered "out of style". Snowboarding has become a sport that encompasses a very diverse international based crowd and fanbase of many millions, so much so that it is no longer possible to stereotype such a large community. Reasons for these dying stereotypes include how mainstream and popular the sport has become, with the shock factor of snowboarding's quick take off on the slopes wearing off. Skiers and snowboarders are becoming used to each other, showing more respect to each other on the mountain. "The typical stereotype of the sport is changing as the demographics change".[37]</description></article><article id="11" ctime="14.12.2017 13:03:37" mtime="14.12.2017 13:03:37" ownerId="candle" categoryId="6" slug="history"><description>According to FIFA, the Chinese competitive game cuju (蹴鞠, literally "kick ball") is the earliest form of football for which there is evidence.[13] Cuju players could use any part of the body apart from hands and the intent was kicking a ball through an opening into a net. It was remarkably similar to modern football, though similarities to rugby occurred.[14][15] During the Han Dynasty (206 BC – 220 AD), cuju games were standardised and rules were established.[14]</description><title>History</title></article><article id="12" ctime="14.12.2017 13:13:07" mtime="14.12.2017 13:13:07" ownerId="user" categoryId="12" slug="preferans"><title>Preferans</title><description>Preferans (Russian: преферанс, IPA: [prʲɪfʲɪˈrans]) is a 10-card plain-trick game with bidding, played by three or four players with a 32-card Piquet deck. It is a sophisticated variant of the Austrian game Préférence, which in turn descends from Spanish Ombre and French Boston.&#13;
&#13;
Popular in Russia since approximately the 1830s, Preferans quickly became the country's national card game. Although superseded in this role by Durak, it is still one of the most popular games in Russia. Similar games are played in various other European countries, from Lithuania to Greece, where an earlier form of Russian Preferans is known as Prefa (Greek: Πρέφα). Compared to Austrian Préférence, Russian Preferans and Greek Prefa are distinguished by the greater number of possible contracts, which allows for almost any combination of trumps and numbers of tricks. Another distinguishing feature is the relatively independent roles played by the opponents of the soloist.</description></article><article id="14" ctime="14.12.2017 15:24:08" mtime="14.12.2017 15:24:08" ownerId="candle" categoryId="2" slug="dummyarticle"><description>dummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy articledummy article</description><title>dummy article</title></article><article id="19" ctime="15.12.2017 22:35:04" mtime="15.12.2017 22:35:04" ownerId="candle" categoryId="7" slug="baseball"><title>Baseball</title><description>Baseball is abat-and-ball game played between two teams of nine players each who take turns batting and fielding. The batting team attempts to score runs by hitting a ball(that is thrown by the opposing team\'spitcher) with a batswung by the batter, and then running counter-clockwise around a series of four bases: first, second, third, and home plate. A run is scored when a player advances around the bases and touches home plate.</description></article></articles>
</sdsapp>
